I dunno know, man.
我不知道啊老兄
Think jobs can't be criminal?
工作就不能是犯罪了
No, not if you're working for the government.
如果给政府打工就不是
You ever hear about the Nuremburg trials, Trev?
你听说过纽伦堡审判吗  特雷弗
They weren't that long ago.
并没过去多久
Yeah
知道
And we hung the Nazi big shots, right?
我们干掉了纳粹的大人物  对吧
Yeah. Well, the big shots were the first trial, but then the next trial
对  大人物都是在第一次审判
were just the judges, and lawyers, and police men, guards.
但是后面的审判就是判那些法官  律师  警察  保安
Ordinary people just doing their jobs. Following orders.
都是些奉命行事的普通人
That's where we got the Nuremberg principles, which then, the UN made into international law
这就是我们得到的纽伦堡原则  然后联合国根据这个制定了国际法
just in case ordinary jobs become criminal again.
以防止普通工作再次变成犯罪